A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 2, Accession 2 FA1184
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges to China, 1977-2010; 3
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: Language Training - Evaluations and Reports, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 351A)
    Restricted - confidential material - Open in 2038.
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - General, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 352)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - Applications, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 353)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - Evaluations and Report, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 354)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - Evaluations and Report, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 354A)
    Restricted - confidential material - Open in 2040.
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: Language Training - General, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 355)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: Language Training - Applications, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 356-357)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: Language Training -Evaluations and Reports, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 358)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - General, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 359)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - Applications, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 360-361)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - Evaluations, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 362)
  - Fulbright- Hays Seminars Abroad: History and Culture - Finances, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 363)
  - Fulbright-Hays Seminars Abroad: Curriculum Projects, 2003-2007, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 364)
    Correspondence and descriptions pertaining to curriculum projects from 2007 seminar groups (Jacobs, Toppler, and Arnold).
  - Fulbright-Hays Seminars Abroad: Curriculum Projects, 2003-2007, 2009; FA1184:051; Digital Media: Binder of 52 CDs and 5 DVDs. Two other CDs and 1 DVD enclosed in binder in individual cases.
    2003 group: Karinsa Moline, Music in China (2 cds); Leslie Martin, China Review; Cori Culp, Tour of China; Christy Schirmer; Ronnie Lynn Holley; Peggy Wenner; Catherine Mein, Palace Museum powerpoint. 2004 group: Jennifer Hall, Traditional Culture of China; S. Kay Mura, China Baroque; Lisa-Anne Culp; Shawn White; whole delegation CD. 2005: Kristina Kafka, Peking Opera; Irina Smith, Journey across China; Scott Schmidt; Peter Samaris; Heather Randolph; Jeffrey Garthee (3 CDs and 1 DVD); JoAnn Ellis; Lisa DosSantos (2 CDs). 2006: Kathy Callahan; Sheila Lantz; Despi Mayes, "The Art of the Brush," Museum Kit Resource Guide and Powerpoint slides; Leslie J. Sutton, Images of China (DVD); Karen Krause; Karen Arms; 1 unlabeled CD. 2007 - Language Training: Cathy Ream, An Introduction to Chinese Culture and History - Powerpoint of a Fulbright experience; Devra Miller, Chinese Students in California (2 CDs); Heidi Draheim; Hye-Young Kim; Virginia von Reichbauer (2 CDs); Jane Hayes; Flora Reichanadter; Laurel Cadwallader (2 CDs): Terri Toppler (2 CDs); Hiroko Kazama (4 CDs?); Carla Arnold, Trip photos, and The Monkey Emperor's Secret performances (4 CDs and 1 DVD). 2007 - History and Culture: Susan Casler; Denise Edelson (2 CDs); Linda K. White; Brian Jacobs; Devra Miller. 2009: Photos by Zhai Guanjun.
  - Fulbright-Hays Seminars Abroad: Housing, Undated, circa 1991; FA1184:026; Still Image: 17 color 3.5 x 5 prints mounted on construction paper. (Box 42, Folder 365)
    Photos of accommodations for Fulbright participants at Beijing Normal University (Beishida). 13 photos of rooms and 4 photos of Chinese men: Hu Min, Li Suosheng, Wang Yingjie, Li Huang.
- Conferences, Seminars, Workshops and Dialogues, 1984-2006; 5
  The Conferences, Seminars, Workshops, and Dialogues documented in RG 2 range in date from 1984 to 2006 and explore issues pertaining to China's emergence as a global player and engagement with China. Topics include Chinese foreign and economic policy, relations with Taiwan and Hong Kong, media coverage of China, and the future of U. S. – China relations. The series particularly includes records of the U. S. – China Dialogues (I – XI, 1984 – 2002), which the National Committee and the Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs initiated as a way of facilitating frank and productive discussion of sensitive issues between the two countries.
  - Greater China Conference: Background and Planning, 1994 May 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Change in the Chinese Economic Area and Its Implications, East-West Center, Honolulu.
  - Greater China Conference: Planning Correspondence, East-West Center, 1994 May 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Greater China Conference, Correspondence with Invitees (U.S., People's Republic of China, Taiwan), 1994 May 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Greater China Conference: Correspondence with Invitees (Hong Kong), 1994 May 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Greater China Conference: Papers and Bios, 1994 May 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Greater China Conference: Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1994 May 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: General, 1995 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Conference on "Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: Status and Prospects," cosponsored with the Committee on Scholarly Communication with China and the Office of Science and Technology Policy. Held at the National Academy of Sciences, Washington, DC.
  - Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: General, 1995 May 4; FA1184:001; Still Images (10 Photos, plus duplicate set). (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Ten photos of conference, plus a duplicate set.
  - Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: Conference Materials, 1995 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: Conference Papers, 1995 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: Financial Report, 1995 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Report to the Ford Foundation.
  - Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: Speaker Bios, 1995 May 4 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sino-American Bilateral Cooperation Agreeements: Rapporteur Report, 1995 May 4 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Anne Thurston was the conference rapporteur.
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference Series Proposal to the Ford Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference, on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Background and Planning, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Conference held at the East-West Center, Honolulu.
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference, on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Invitation Letters, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference, on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Acceptances, Regrets, and Participant Bios, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference, on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Correspondence with Invitees, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference, on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Correspondence with the East-West Center, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference, on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Correspondence with Great Britain, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference, on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Correspondence with Japan, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Namelist and Conference Notes, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Two sets of notes by Jan Berris and unidentified (David M. Lampton?).
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Travel, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference on the Emergence of China into the Global Community: Follow-Up and Thank Yous, 1994 December 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Includes report to the Ford Foundation.
  - G-7 plus 3 Conference at Ditchley, 1995 October 20-22 (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
    China after Deng: Policy Implications. Conference held at Ditchley Park, Oxfordshire.
  - G-7 Conference in Japan, 1997 April 2-4 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    International China Seminar, China in Multiple Transition and the World.
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Proposal, Budget, and Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Grant from the Smith Richardson Foundation to the NCUSCR, for conferences, research, and the production of an edited volume of papers on The Making of Chinese Foreign and Security Policy in the Era of Reform, 1978-2000.
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Proposal, Budget, and Correspondence, 1996-2000; FA1184:052; Bound Volume (Box 42, Folder 27)
    The Making of Chinese Foreign and Security Policy in the Era of Reform.
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Chapter Proposals, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Rejection Letters, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Contracts with Writers and Honoraria, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Publisher Correspondence and Editing, 1997-1998, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Westfields Conference, 1998 February 27 - March 1 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Project conference on Making of Chinese Foreign and Security Policy in the Era of Reform, Westfields Conference Center, Chantilly, VA.
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Westfields Conference (Papers), 1998 February 27-March 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Making of Chinese Foreign and Security Policy in the Era of Reform, first project conference.
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Comments on First Drafts, 1998 March (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Field Research (Travel Reimbursement), 1998 Summer - Fall (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Chapter Writers' Conference, 1999 February 19-20 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Project conference on Making of Chinese Foreign and Security Policy in the Era of Reform, Madison Hotel, Washington, DC.
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Chapter Writers' Conference (Papers) (1 of 2), 1999 February 19-20 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Making of Chinese Foreign and Security Policy in the Era of Reform, second project conference.
  - Smith Richardson Grant Project: Chapter Writers' Conference (Papers) (2 of 2), 1999 February 19-20 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Planning, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    United States - China Relations: Where Do We Go from Here?
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Funders, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Smith Richardson Foundation.
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Invitation Letters, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Conference Packet, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Includes participant bios and additional readings.
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Briefing Book, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Additional Readings, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Notes and Follow-Up, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Report, 1999 July 25-27 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S. - China Relations: Report, 1999 July 25-27; FA1184:031; Digital Media: Floppy disk, National Committee, Airlie Center Conference
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): General, 1998 May 6-8 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Includes Agenda, Invitation Letters and Participant Bios.
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): Proposals and Background, 1998 May 6-8 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Conference on United States Media Coverage of China. Grant funding received from the MacArthur Foundation.
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): Planning Correspondence, 1998 May 6-8 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): Briefing Kit (Master), 1998 May 6-8 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): Bibliography and Supplemental Readings, 1998 May 6-8 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): Conference Packet, 1998 May 6-8 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): Attendence Checklists, 1998 May 6-8 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Media Conference (U. S. Coverage of China): Report and Follow-Up, 1998 May 6-8 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    Includes report distribution.
  - China on the World Stage: Reexamining Expectations, 1999 October 28 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    Conference at National Press Club, Washington, DC, cosponsored by the International Research aand Exchanges Board (IREX).
  - China on the World Stage: Reexamining Expectations, 1999 October 28; FA1184:002; Still Image: 9 snapshots (Box 42, Folder 56)
    Jan Berris and other panelists at conference.
  - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Conference Packet and Readings, 2000 July 14-16 (Box 7, Folder 57-58)
    Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role, Pocantico Conference Center, NY.
  - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Briefing Book, 2000 July 14-16 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    File appears to contain supplemental readings.
  - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Budget, Funding, and Venue, 2000 July 14-16 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Participants, 2000 July 14-16 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    Includes invitation letters and thank yous.
  - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Report, 2000 July 14-16 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role.
  - Role of the Media in a Market Economy: General Planning and Budget, 2002 November 20-21 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    Conference in Beijing, cosponsored with Tsinghua University. Also described as Financial Media Conference or Delegation.
  - Role of the Media in a Market Economy: Background, 2002 November 20-21 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    Papers and correspondence.
  - Role of the Media in a Market Economy: MacArthur Foundation, 2002 November 20-21 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    Correspondence.
  - Role of the Media in a Market Economy: Papers, 2002 November 20-21 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Role of the Media in a Market Economy: Participants, 2002 November 20-21 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Includes Itinerary and Namelists
  - Role of the Media in a Market Economy: Participants, 2002 November 20-21; FA1184:003; Still Image (Box 42, Folder 67)
    Two group photos.
  - Role of the Media in a Market Economy: Report and Follow-Up, 2002 November 20-21 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Cross-Strait Conference: General, 2003 August 8-10 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role. Pocantico Conference Center. Agenda, participant list, correspondence, and follow-up.
  - Cross-Strait Conference: Proposals and Funding, 2003 August 8-10 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Cross-Strait Conference: Invitations, 2003 August 8-10 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Cross-Strait Conference: Conference Packet, 2003 August 8-10 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Cross-Strait Conference: Notes, 2003 August 8-10 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Foreign Aid Policy Workshop: General, 2005 November 29-30 (Box 9, Folder 74-75)
    Beijing.
  - Foreign Aid Policy Workshop: Report, 2005 November 29-30 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Central - Local Fiscal Relations in China Conference, 2006 July 10-11 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    Beijing. Includes proposal to the Ford Foundation.
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Background and Planning, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    Next Generation of Cross-Strait Interlocutors: Conflict Management Resolution Workshop. San Diego.
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Correspondence, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Applicants, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Budget and Finances, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Program Materials and Notes, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Readings, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Evaluations and Follow-Up, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Conflict Management Workshop: Related and Future Programs, 2006 August 5-14 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - International NGOs and China, 2006 November 29 (Box 10, Folder 86-87)
    International NGOs and China: An Assessment. Asia Society.
  - United States - China Dialogue: Background and Planning, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Advisory Group, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Funding, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Correspondence with Chinese, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Chinese Delegation Visit, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    Includes brochure, namelists, guidelines, and itinerary.
  - United States - China Dialogue: Participants, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Papers, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Report, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Press Coverage and Follow-Up, 1984 September 6-9 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Other Dialogues, 1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 97)
    Correspondence and reference file on dialogues sponsored by other organizations.
  - Second United States - China Dialogue: Background and Planning, 1985 October 10-25 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Second United States - China Dialogue: Participants, 1985 October 10-25 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Second United States - China Dialogue: Briefing Materials, 1985 October 10-25 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Second United States - China Dialogue: Report and Summary Notes, 1985 October 10-25 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Second United States - China Dialogue: Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1985 October 10-25 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Third United States - China Dialogue: General, 1987 April 2-5 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    Wingspread Conference Center. Includes conference booklet, transcripts of speeches, and correspondence with the Johnson Foundation.
  - Third United States - China Dialogue: Background and Planning, 1987 April 2-5 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Third United States - China Dialogue: Background Materials, 1987 April 2-5 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Third United States - China Dialogue: Conference Summaries, 1987 April 2-5 (Box 12, Folder 106-107)
  - Third United States - China Dialogue: Conference Summaries, 1987 April 2-5; FA1184:027; Audio: Cassette tape
    Binational 1987 - Anne Thurston's Notes.
  - Third United States - China Dialogue: Chinese Delegation Trip, 1987 March 27 - April 12 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Third United States - China Dialogue: Reports, 1987 April 2-5 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Fourth United States - China Dialogue (Postponed): General, 1989 June 21-24 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Fourth United States - China Dialogue (Postponed): Background Materials, 1989 June 21-24 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Fourth United-States - China Dialogue: Correspondence, 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Fourth United-States - China Dialogue: Background and Planning, 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Fourth United-States - China Dialogue: Background Material, 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    Asia-Pacific Report, East-West Center, 1989. Focus: China in the Reform Era.
  - Fourth United States - China Dialogue: Participants and Itinerary, 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    Includes set of color photocopies of conference participants (original photos not found).
  - Fourth United States - China Dialogue: Notes, 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    Notes by Jan Berris added to file.
  - Fourth United-States - China Dialogue: Statements and Remarks, 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    Foreign Affairs Journal, Beijing, No. 16, June 1990, added to this file (includes excerpts from speeches).
  - Fourth United-States-China Dialogue: Summary Report, 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Fourth United-States-China Dialogue: Summary Report (Draft), 1990 February 26-March 1 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - United States - China Dialogue: Briefing Book and Notes, 1990 October 22-23 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    Washington, DC. Topic: China - U.S. Relations in a Changing World.
  - Fifth United States - China Dialogue: Background and Planning Correspondence, 1991 June 14-17 (Box 14, Folder 121-122)
    Wingspread Conference Center.
  - Fifth United States - China Dialogue: Background Materials, 1991 June 14-17 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Fifth United States - China Dialogue: Participants, 1991 June 14-17 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Fifth United States - China Dialogue: Chinese Delegation Meetings and Trip, 1991 June 12-23 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Fifth United States - China Dialogue: Program Book and Notes, 1991 June 14-17 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Fifth United States - China Dialogue: Papers and Reports, 1991 June 14-17 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Fifth United States - China Dialogue: Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1991 June 14-17 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Sixth United States - China Dialogue: General, 1993 March 31 - April 10 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    Beijing. Includes Agenda and Itineraries.
  - Sixth United States - China Dialogue: General, 1993 March 31 - April 10; FA1184:004; Still Images: 2 6x8 color prints. (Box 42, Folder 129)
    Two images of Dialogue participants (Ambassador Roy, Barber Conable, Premier Li Peng, and Ambassador Liu Shuqing).
  - Sixth United States - China Dialogue: Background and Planning, 1993 March 31 - April 10 (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - Sixth United States - China Dialogue: Participants, 1993 March 31 - April 10 (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - Sixth United States - China Dialogue: Hong Kong Program, 1993 March 31 - April 10 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    Breakfast Briefing in Hong Kong, April 10.
  - Sixth United States - China Dialogue: Thematic Summary Report and Discussion with Premier Li Peng, 1993 April 1-3 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Sixth United States - China Dialogue: Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1993 March 31 - April 10 (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Seventh United States - China Dialogue: Background and Planning, 1994 October 7-10 (Box 16, Folder 135-136)
    Pocantico Conference Center.
  - Seventh United States - China Dialogue: Correspondence with Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs (CPIFA) (Zhang Wenpu), 1994 October 7-10 (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - Seventh United States - China Dialogue: Participants, 1994 October 7-10 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Seventh United States - China Dialogue: Chinese Delegation Meetings and Trip, 1994 October 5-15 (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - Seventh United States - China Dialogue: Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1994 October 7-10 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    Includes Final Financial Report to the Ford Foundation on the Binational Dialogue Project, 1993-1995.
  - Eighth United States - China Dialogue (Postponed): Correspondence, 1995 November 30 - December 10 (Box 16, Folder 141-142)
  - Eighth United States - China Dialogue (Postponed): American Participants, 1995 November 30 - December 10 (Box 16, Folder 143)
    Includes passport photos of delegates (not separated from file).
  - Eighth United States - China Dialogue (Postponed): Imbroglio, 1995 November 30 - December 10 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Eighth United States - China Dialogue (Postponed): Andrew Nathan file, 1995 November 30 - December 10 (Box 17, Folder 145)